<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Counter-Strike 2 - News (English)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml</link>
    <description>Counter-Strike 2 News Feed</description>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 01:57:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Armory</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4674264042200250912?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's update introduces the Armory, all new Weapon Charms, and a whole lot more. Click the image below for more details!<br/><a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armory?snr=" tabindex="0"><span><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/4f30364bf12221dd5c8db6fa9f113fee1e8b0641.png"/></span></a>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4674264042200250912</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side-stepping Skill</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/6500469346429600836?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counter-Strike is constantly evolving. From art, to maps, to inventive plays, and even player input, the CS community shapes the game. <br/><br/>Scripting and automating player commands has always been contentious, but over the years some forms of scripting (e.g., jump-throws) have gained acceptance, as they enable plays that wouldn't otherwise be possible. In fact, jump-throws became such an important part of the game that we've done the work to make them reliable without any special scripting or binds (i.e., by jumping and quickly throwing a grenade).<br/><br/>Developing one's coordination and reaction time has always been key to mastering Counter-Strike.<br/><br/>Recently, some hardware features have blurred the line between manual input and automation, so we've decided to draw a clear line on what is or isn't acceptable in Counter-Strike.<br/><br/>We are no longer going to allow automation (via scripting or hardware) that circumvent these core skills and, moving forward, (and initially--exclusively on Valve Official Servers) players suspected of automating multiple player actions from a single game input may be kicked from their match.<br/><br/>To prevent accidental infractions, in-game binds that include more than one movement and/or attack actions will no longer work (e.g., null-binds and jump-throw binds).<br/><br/>If you have a keyboard that includes an input-automation feature (e.g., "Snap Tap Mode"), be sure to disable the feature before you join a match in order to avoid any interruption to your matches.<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6500469346429600836</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Season</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/7090437900079084674?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<a class="Focusable" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.counter-strike.net%2Fnewsentry%2F3677802763035982969" rel="noopener nofollow" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="counter-strike.net">Last year</span></a> we announced the broad strokes of new rules for professional Counter-Strike events, to take effect in 2025. Today, we're filling in the details--click <a class="Focusable" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FValveSoftware%2Fcounter-strike_rules_and_regs%2Fblob%2Fmain%2Ftournament-operation-requirements.md" rel="noopener nofollow" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="github.com">here</span></a> to see the terms that will be added to Tournament Organizers' license agreements moving forward.<br/><br/>Counter-Strike is at its best when teams compete on a level playing field, and these new rules are part of our commitment to the long-term health of Counter-Strike as a sport. Our goal is to ensure that professional Counter-Strike remains an open sport, where teams are only limited by their ability.<br/><br/>Although we expect that there will be some rough edges as we transition to the new requirements, we're excited to see what the future will bring.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7090437900079084674</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Real MVP</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4194621169493598732?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the launch of CS2, community map mappers have been hard at work creating new experiences and updating some classics. Today, we're excited to add the first community maps to CS2!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/bbf2dd17698bcba8bae487ca7a0783a441581476.png"/><br/>For those of you who dream of Italian weddings, or airplane manufacture (or both!), we've got you covered. Memento and Assembly are now available in Wingman.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/df15c710ff065c92619e712ecf6ee4492e93ac27.png"/><br/>And if you're in the mood for something a bit more... chaotic, take a dip in the classic Pool Day, which is now available in Arms Race.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d2ad077ed631514103c5eb83183790cd4829a5f6.png"/><br/>Finally, fight your way through the streets of Thera and Mills in Deathmatch and Casual, and put these maps through their paces in Competitive Matchmaking. <br/><br/>Speaking of Competitive Matchmaking, we've given map-based skill groups an overhaul. In addition to redistributing players across the Skill Groups, we've also made it easier to earn those badges in the first place.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/dda0b5f6d6fa18ac9274627c2b8a5e393d645ad0.png"/><br/><br/>There are a bunch of other fixes and adjustments in today's update, including a brand new MVP panel (and animated MVPs in Premier!) and new ways to optimize your video settings. <br/><br/>Jump into a match and check it out!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4194621169493598732</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4177730135016204539?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's update includes some love for the CT economy, with price cuts to the M4A4 and Incendiary grenade, and a bit less cash going to the T's when the bomb gets defused.<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/07975a254ee44f0d2674f271a21204d0761ec85d.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/4b75b3b9464ad1389e13d65911781ada4dda3f47.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e54cfc1edae4997920e5db8145edeb377af94fc1.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/><br/>In addition to the price cut, the incendiary grenade has gotten a bit of a makeover with a new visual treatment for its explosion and flames, and reduced spread and duration. <br/><br/>And in other gameplay news, Vertigo's A-site has gotten some significant changes--it's now the site featured in Wingman matches, so check it out.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/955406bdcb60dba4a59ce0926fdd180946b7d9bb.png"/><br/><br/>Calling all Kilowatt Collection fans! Now, when you open a Kilowatt case with a key, you'll be given the option to rent the whole collection for a week (excluding the rare special item) instead of keeping a single item. You can play with the weapons as much as you like during that week, but they can't be modified by stickers or nametags.<br/><br/>Lots of other changes in today's update, including some quality of life improvements for demo playback, slightly smarter chickens, and a bit of spring cleaning--good news for fans of 'various bug fixes.'<br/><br/>Jump into a match and see what's new!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4177730135016204539</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Other Hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4202497395512481609?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's update includes a bunch of quality-of-life improvements that touch upon every part of the game, from maps to UI to gameplay. A few highlights are below, but check out the <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/730/view/4202497395513061959?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">release notes</span></a> to see what's new!<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2723ea38b9ba52592038731f15e5e9ba512be979.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/1a9b430c3ae10f5ec94a27d24f87187618d1919a.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/758e01194008b2d20797a378de390cdc24305cf9.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/>Lefties rejoice! Players can now redeploy their weapons, swapping between the left and right hand. You can set your preferred handedness in the settings menu and then switch hands temporarily mid-round with a key press (H on US Keyboards by default).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/897b47892c65929ccd471ccff7d5aa65696eeb6f.png"/><br/>The buy menu has a few new tricks. To help you decide whether to buy or save, the top right of the buy menu now features the minimum amount of money you're guaranteed to have next round (thanks Kadomos). And at the bottom you'll find the new 'Dropped Weapons' panel, where you can see (and directly pick up) any weapons that you or teammates have dropped in the buy zone.<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/f1462b7eefe16c70d61291b8676b1a404688da37.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e14db7419e60d31e09ed7d199683561d061bbc17.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/ce366b2eaaf9211f367b50eec46533f8f99ba207.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/>There are several more HUD/UI changes in today's update. For those of you who have memorized a library of grenade line-ups, a line-up reticle will appear shortly after you pull the pin (you can even customize the delay for each grenade type). And if you've had trouble navigating through smoke, set a Radar Map Alternate Zoom and add a Toggle Radar Zoom key binding, which will let you switch between zoom levels during a round.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/ac9e7e5f1f6386cfec4de86e771a6fdc7206471c.png"/><br/>We've updated the Active Duty map pool (for both Premier and competitions), removing Overpass and bringing back Dust II. And there are changes to many other maps, including significant changes to Inferno.<br/><br/>Jump right into a match and see what's new, or practice with your friends--practice matches and workshop maps can now be launched with members of your party.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4202497395512481609</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copenhagen Major Champions</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4185606994270578198?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/75c3204fcb2874385f7c3e1dafeb00003b76502e.png"/><br/>Congratulations to Natus Vincere, the first CS2 Major Champions!<br/><br/>Playing in front of a sold-out arena and with over 1.8 million viewers watching around the world, NAVI and FaZe met in the Grand Final of one of the most hotly-contested Counter-Strike Majors of all time. Trading map wins in Ancient and Mirage, the teams moved to Inferno for the decider. There, b1t, jL, Aleksib, iM, and w0nderful put on a dominating performance to earn the trophy and title of Major Champions.<br/><br/>To celebrate their achievement, the Copenhagen 2024 Major Champions Capsule is now available for purchase. The capsule features autographs for each member of the winning team in paper, glitter, holo, and gold. 50% of the proceeds go to the players and organizations.<br/><br/>And with that, the Copenhagen Major has come to a close. See you next time in Shanghai!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4185606994270578198</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Championship Sunday in Copenhagen</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4167591962341209737?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d127fb6e4685f88d2921a5735ccba009dc2ff68d.png"/><br/>The Semifinals of the Copenhagen Major featured four titans of Counter-Strike; FaZe Clan versus Team Vitality and Natus Vincere versus G2 Esports.<br/> <br/>And the Semifinalists delivered! Both matchups required all three maps to determine a winner, and when the dust settled FaZe Clan and Natus Vincere were left standing. They will go head-to-head in the Grand Finals of Counter-Strike 2’s first Major Championship.<br/><br/>Championship Sunday begins with the Showmatch, beginning at 18:15 CET. The Grand Finals begin at 20:00 CET.<br/><br/>As the Major comes to a close there’s still time to support your favorite teams and players. Tournament items are available in-game, with 50% of the proceeds going to the players, teams, and organizations participating in the PGL Copenhagen Major. <br/><br/>See you Sunday!<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4167591962341209737</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copenhagen Playoffs and Pick’Ems</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4104540932633328367?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/b80e4de648288b7a193fb2218f6c6c6b348fa18a.png"/><br/>The Elimination Stage of the PGL Copenhagen Major has concluded, leaving eight teams to compete for Counter-Strike 2’s first Major Championship.<br/><br/>Congratulations to Team Spirit and MOUZ who advanced unbeaten, finishing with a perfect 3-0 record. Eternal Fire, Cloud9, and Team Vitality each went 3-1, and Natus Vincere, G2 Esports, and FaZe Clan went the distance, needing all five matches to advance with 3-2 records.<br/><br/>Playoff matches begin Thursday, March 28th from Royal Arena in Copenhagen, Denmark. Predictions for the Pick’Em Challenge are due before the first Playoff match begins, so lock in your picks now!<br/><br/>And don’t forget, team and player stickers are available now, with 50% of the proceeds going to the players, teams, and organizations participating in the PGL Copenhagen Major.<br/><br/>Good luck and have fun!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4104540932633328367</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGL Copenhagen 2024: Stickers!</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4104540932612285123?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The opening stage of the PGL Copenhagen Major has come to a close and storylines are rapidly developing. New rosters are rising to the occasion. Seasoned teams are reaching peak form at the perfect time. Asia and the Americas have come roaring back to life. Who will reach the playoffs? Tune in to the Elimination stage and find out!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d58744721b2c90bc58597bd0aeee173411b2c185.png"/><br/>If you've been looking for a way to show your support for your favorite teams, now is your chance. Team and Player Autograph sticker capsules are now available for purchase in the Copenhagen Major hub. You'll find all of the players and teams at the Major, split into capsules featuring paper, glitter, holo, and gold stickers. 50% of the proceeds go to the players and organizations participating in the Major.<br/><br/>For those of you playing the Pick'Em Challenge, don't forget to set your picks before the first Elimination stage matches!<br/><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4104540932612285123</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGL Copenhagen 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/6727887174668178386?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In December, hundreds of teams from around the world began their long journey to the first Counter-Strike 2 Major. Fighting through open, closed, and regional qualifiers--now only 24 remain. Tune in to the PGL Copenhagen Major on March 17th and watch the best Counter-Strike teams in the world battle for the title of Major Champion!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/928b9520fe984786a92fbffb671023a42770d990.png"/><br/>Today we're shipping the all-new Copenhagen Major Hub, where you can find the Pick'Em Challenge, the Copenhagen 2024 Viewer Pass, Souvenirs, and (coming soon) Team and Player stickers. 50% of the proceeds from tournament items are shared with players and organizations.<br/><br/>Playing the Pick'Em Challenge with an active pass will give you a chance to upgrade your Copenhagen 2024 Coin and earn extra Souvenir Packages. You'll also show up on the Active Pass Leaderboard, where you can compare your Pick'Em Challenge performance to your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e819d0a262182a891fcd7e8970f43e65b6072106.png"/><br/>In the past, you needed an active pass to play the Pick'Em game. No more! Now, everyone with Prime status can place their picks for free. However, to complete challenges and earn rewards from each event stage, you'll have to activate your pass before the stage begins.<br/><br/>So place your picks and get ready to cheer for your favorite teams. The PGL Copenhagen 2024 Major is almost here!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6727887174668178386</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Call to Arms</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4064004264605245458?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armsrace?snr=" tabindex="0"><span><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/aaae97dfe5530d92066a520ee5f83b233e926a0b.png"/></span></a><br/>Arms Race has returned! Grab your guns and brace yourself for a chaotic race to the top. Get two kills with each weapon to reach the final stage, or steal your opponents’ progress with your knife (or now with the Zeus)! Work your way up to the knife stage and earn the final kill to secure the win.<br/><br/>There's a lot more shipping today, from custom sticker placement to new content to gameplay updates. Click <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armsrace?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">here</span></a> to learn more!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4064004264605245458</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 Service Medal</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/6107508076983703492?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/6eba6fdad2eeb08061c08631ae1ebe7e14099427.png"/><br/><br/>Celebrate your time in CS2 with the all-new 2024 Service Medal, available starting January 1st!<br/><br/>To get your service medal, earn XP by playing in official game modes and rank up your CS2 Profile. When you reach Global General (Rank 40), you'll have the option to reset your Profile Rank and earn (or upgrade) a 2024 Service Medal. The medal is an inspectable display item you can show off wherever your avatar is shown.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6107508076983703492</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Maps Workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3787024475483064536?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/9b5fa738bb8617b7799066bedc75c1ab47ce6b23.png"/><br/>The Maps workshop is now open for business.<br/><br/>Community map makers can start uploading their maps to the workshop, and community servers can host those maps. If you'd like to try some workshop maps offline, subscribe to them on the workshop and head to the Play menu.<br/><br/>There are a bunch of other workshop tool updates today, along with a host of other fixes and adjustments to CS2. Check out the notes, play some matches, and keep that feedback coming!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3787024475483064536</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Home</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3747614808335282785?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/8d881c9e69922ab988c6304052979d16bc920346.png"/><br/>Counter-Strike 2 is here.<br/><br/>Come take a look around. Counter-Strike 2 is the largest technical leap forward in Counter-Strike's history, supporting new features today and updates for years to come.<br/><br/>If you're a returning player you'll find your favorite maps and matchmaking modes right where you left them, along with a revamped Premier mode where you can establish your all-new CS Rating. Rise through the ranks and see where you stand on global and regional leaderboards.<br/><br/>For new players, learn the basics with some offline training and jump into Casual and Deathmatch to hone your skills. Once you've unlocked Competitive matchmaking you'll be off to the races.<br/><br/>Grab your friends, and come join millions of players around the world. Welcome to Counter-Strike 2.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3747614808335282785</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
