<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Counter-Strike 2 - News (English)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml</link>
    <description>Counter-Strike 2 News Feed</description>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 01:53:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Season's Greetings</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/520830071182721028?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Welcome to Premier Season Two. <br/><br/>If you haven't heard the news, here's what's new in Season Two. Vertigo is out, Train is in, the M4A4 is more... A4-dable... and we've tweaked the FAMAS. <br/><br/>Season Two runs from now through the Austin Major, at which point players who meet the requirements will be awarded a Premier Season Two Medal. The color will correspond to your highest CS Rating achieved during the season, and the bars will reflect your total wins, with one bar for every 25—up to five bars.<br/><br/>To earn your Premier Season Two Medal, you'll need an account in good standing, 25 Premier match wins, and an active CSR at the end of the season.<br/><br/>Premier matchmaking is now open for business, so hit the queue and start racking up those wins!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">520830071182721028</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seasons Change</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/520829437562848128?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/752a115784870febdc4da7bf1b4bd2fdaea0d3d5.png"/><br/>Next week we will say "goodbye" to Premier Season One, and "hello" to Season Two. To celebrate, every player who earned a CS Rating during Season One will receive a commemorative Premier Season One Medal. Your medal includes detailed Season Statistics that you can view by clicking on the medal in your inventory. Review your Season One highs and lows with graphs of your CSR and playtime, or view your map-specific stats to find areas of improvement for Season Two.<br/><br/>As we transition to Season Two, there'll be one day of Premier downtime during which your CS Rating will be recalibrated for the new season based on your Season One performance. At the start of the new Season you will need to re-establish your CS Rating by winning 10 matches.<br/><br/><video autoplay="" crossorigin="anonymous" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d495453498221843cfda536124bcc4fcc900047b.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/6e803fe05de9235ccca66ba9fdcd8a083d4ff55a.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/fed939de66b4f14899ed743a4201d163b260341a.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/>Season Two comes with some changes. Train is in and Vertigo is out, the M4A4 is a bit less expensive, and the FAMAS has some improvements to its standing and crouching accuracy (along with a price cut).<br/><br/>And when Season Two comes to a close after the Austin Major, players who meet the requirements will be awarded a Premier Season Two Medal. The color will correspond to your highest CS Rating achieved during the season, and the bars will reflect your total wins, with one bar for every 25—up to five bars.<br/><br/>To earn your Premier Season Two Medal, you'll need an account in good standing, 25 Premier match wins, and an active CSR at the end of the season.<br/><br/>So clear out your calendar, because Season Two is about to begin!<br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">520829437562848128</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champions of Shanghai</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529833471389991079?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c832bcc989b6e03012fde727c077c846d245cb22.jpg"/><br/>The Perfect World Shanghai Grand Final was one to remember. Team Spirit and FaZe Clan needed all three maps to determine a champion in front of an excited, sold-out crowd at the SPD Bank Oriental Sports Center.<br/><br/>Down 12:5 on map 3, FaZe Clan battled back with 6 consecutive round wins—and some incredible clutches along the way—to force round 24. With the bomb planted and down to a 1v1, sh1ro's final kill earned Team Spirit their first Major Championship.<br/><br/>Celebrate Team Spirit's win with the Major Champions Capsule, now available for purchase. The capsule features autographs from Team Spirit in paper, glitter, holo, and gold, and 50% of the proceeds go to the players and organizations.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/3ed2c31143f07013ef30373c1458adc84731c04d.png"/><br/>With Shanghai in the books we look forward to the BLAST.tv Major in Austin, Texas. See you in June 2025!<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">2025 Service Medal</div><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/7f0747f83da9da8ed752f3848e0ab17caf40de9d.png"/><br/>Beginning January 1st, 2025 players can receive the newest Service Medal in-game. <br/><br/>When you reach Global General (Rank 40) you'll have the option to reset your Profile Rank and earn (or upgrade) a 2025 Service Medal.<br/><br/>Good luck and have fun!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529833471389991079</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowning a Champion in Shanghai</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/707725115500004414?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/367dbffc57e14f6f9beda4743c8d6a4c349309de.png"/><br/>After an exciting Playoff Stage, FaZe Clan and Team Spirit are the last two standing and will meet in the Grand Finals of the Perfect World Shanghai Major.<br/><br/>On one side of the Playoff bracket, FaZe Clan defeated Team Vitality 2-1 and G2 Esports 2-0 to reach the Grand Finals for the second consecutive Major. <br/><br/>On the other side, Team Spirit overwhelmed Team Liquid 2-0, then outlasted MOUZ 2-1 on their way to the organization's first Major Grand Finals appearance.<br/><br/>The Grand Finals begin on December 15th at 01:00 PST and the Showmatch takes place two hours prior. Don't miss a moment!<br/><br/>And don't forget, team and player stickers are still available, with 50% of the proceeds going to the players, teams, and organizations participating in the Perfect World Shanghai Major.<br/><br/>Best of luck to both teams!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">707725115500004414</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2024 Perfect World Shanghai Major Playoffs</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/528706478197966784?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e8cd3a6061a551832aedce4be89115144316051d.png"/><br/>The Elimination Stage of the 2024 Perfect World Shanghai Major delivered memorable plays, breathtaking clutches, and some of the best 1vX moments in recent memory. And now the final eight teams will battle in front of sold-out crowds at the SPD Bank Oriental Sports Center to become Major Champions.<br/><br/>The MongolZ and Team Vitality finished the Elimination Stage with perfect 3-0 records. G2 Esports, Team Spirit, and Team Liquid went 3-1, and HEROIC, FaZe Clan, and MOUZ advanced at 3-2.<br/><br/>The first Playoff match begins Wednesday, December 11th at 22:00 PST between The MongolZ and MOUZ, and all Playoff picks for the Pick'Em Challenge must be made before the match begins!<br/><br/>As the Major enters its final stage, team and player stickers are still available, with 50% of the proceeds going to the players, teams, and organizations participating in the Perfect World Shanghai Major.<br/><br/>Good luck to the final eight teams!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">528706478197966784</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai 2024 Major</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4472732402493426409?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Counter-Strike Major has come to Shanghai.<br/><br/>Over the past month, teams from around the world challenged the best in their region for their spot in the Major. Now the dust has settled and 24 teams remain--perennial favorites, seasoned veterans, and more than a few newcomers.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/f0f38a64ad92793e959eec2a45ff34098daf8f38.png"/><br/>The Shanghai Major Hub is now open for business, complete with the Pick'Em Challenge, the Shanghai 2024 Viewer Pass, Souvenirs, Graffiti, and Team and Player stickers. 50% of the proceeds from tournament items are shared with players and organizations.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/56dc2ad026cabb70fc939f0dfa95c9bf4227dce4.png"/><br/>The Pick'Em Challenge is free to play, but if you want to upgrade your Shanghai 2024 Coin (and earn extra Souvenir Packages), make sure to activate your Viewer Pass before the event begins. You can also compare your Pick'Em performance to other friends with active passes on the Active Pass Leaderboard.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2a940af901af1afe7527f1fb2eb7c2e9e51d3e32.png"/><br/>It's time to support your favorite teams. Place your picks, set your graffiti, mark your calendar and get ready, because the Shanghai Major is about to begin. May the best team win!<br/><br/><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4472732402493426409</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Aboard!</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4458095069430284354?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We're happy to announce the return of the momentarily lost classic, Train.<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2cc311b50abe04bf2c3700216fb80f9a9aa26c36.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/bb2e4dbe98255eb95e5aac9fa0728ff4310b07bb.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d9eb0bc560630c27136b997f3f171de4b8176394.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/><br/>There's plenty of classic Counter-Strike in every inch of this map—but we also made sure to mix up the gameplay a bit to keep you Train veterans on your toes. We also gave it a full visual overhaul, which means your favorite bleak Eastern European train yard is now 60% cloudier. With a chance of rain? We guarantee it.<br/><br/>So queue up and get ready to master the newest version of one of Counter-Strike's most iconic maps. Train is now available in casual and competitive game modes.<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">Overpass Updates and New Community Maps</div><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/9f20d9e437f8ae93c6f276546599860361b0a50b.png"/><br/>Overpass has received a number of updates based on community feedback, and we're adding four new community maps to the game. Basalt returns to Counter-Strike 2 alongside Edin in casual and competitive game modes, and Palais and Whistle have been added to Wingman.<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4458095069430284354</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Armory</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4674264042200250912?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's update introduces the Armory, all new Weapon Charms, and a whole lot more. Click the image below for more details!<br/><a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armory?snr=" tabindex="0"><span><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/4f30364bf12221dd5c8db6fa9f113fee1e8b0641.png"/></span></a>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4674264042200250912</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side-stepping Skill</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/6500469346429600836?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counter-Strike is constantly evolving. From art, to maps, to inventive plays, and even player input, the CS community shapes the game. <br/><br/>Scripting and automating player commands has always been contentious, but over the years some forms of scripting (e.g., jump-throws) have gained acceptance, as they enable plays that wouldn't otherwise be possible. In fact, jump-throws became such an important part of the game that we've done the work to make them reliable without any special scripting or binds (i.e., by jumping and quickly throwing a grenade).<br/><br/>Developing one's coordination and reaction time has always been key to mastering Counter-Strike.<br/><br/>Recently, some hardware features have blurred the line between manual input and automation, so we've decided to draw a clear line on what is or isn't acceptable in Counter-Strike.<br/><br/>We are no longer going to allow automation (via scripting or hardware) that circumvent these core skills and, moving forward, (and initially--exclusively on Valve Official Servers) players suspected of automating multiple player actions from a single game input may be kicked from their match.<br/><br/>To prevent accidental infractions, in-game binds that include more than one movement and/or attack actions will no longer work (e.g., null-binds and jump-throw binds).<br/><br/>If you have a keyboard that includes an input-automation feature (e.g., "Snap Tap Mode"), be sure to disable the feature before you join a match in order to avoid any interruption to your matches.<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6500469346429600836</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Season</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/7090437900079084674?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<a class="Focusable" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.counter-strike.net%2Fnewsentry%2F3677802763035982969" rel="noopener nofollow" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="counter-strike.net">Last year</span></a> we announced the broad strokes of new rules for professional Counter-Strike events, to take effect in 2025. Today, we're filling in the details--click <a class="Focusable" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FValveSoftware%2Fcounter-strike_rules_and_regs%2Fblob%2Fmain%2Ftournament-operation-requirements.md" rel="noopener nofollow" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="github.com">here</span></a> to see the terms that will be added to Tournament Organizers' license agreements moving forward.<br/><br/>Counter-Strike is at its best when teams compete on a level playing field, and these new rules are part of our commitment to the long-term health of Counter-Strike as a sport. Our goal is to ensure that professional Counter-Strike remains an open sport, where teams are only limited by their ability.<br/><br/>Although we expect that there will be some rough edges as we transition to the new requirements, we're excited to see what the future will bring.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7090437900079084674</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Real MVP</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4194621169493598732?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the launch of CS2, community map mappers have been hard at work creating new experiences and updating some classics. Today, we're excited to add the first community maps to CS2!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/bbf2dd17698bcba8bae487ca7a0783a441581476.png"/><br/>For those of you who dream of Italian weddings, or airplane manufacture (or both!), we've got you covered. Memento and Assembly are now available in Wingman.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/df15c710ff065c92619e712ecf6ee4492e93ac27.png"/><br/>And if you're in the mood for something a bit more... chaotic, take a dip in the classic Pool Day, which is now available in Arms Race.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d2ad077ed631514103c5eb83183790cd4829a5f6.png"/><br/>Finally, fight your way through the streets of Thera and Mills in Deathmatch and Casual, and put these maps through their paces in Competitive Matchmaking. <br/><br/>Speaking of Competitive Matchmaking, we've given map-based skill groups an overhaul. In addition to redistributing players across the Skill Groups, we've also made it easier to earn those badges in the first place.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/dda0b5f6d6fa18ac9274627c2b8a5e393d645ad0.png"/><br/><br/>There are a bunch of other fixes and adjustments in today's update, including a brand new MVP panel (and animated MVPs in Premier!) and new ways to optimize your video settings. <br/><br/>Jump into a match and check it out!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4194621169493598732</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4177730135016204539?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's update includes some love for the CT economy, with price cuts to the M4A4 and Incendiary grenade, and a bit less cash going to the T's when the bomb gets defused.<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/07975a254ee44f0d2674f271a21204d0761ec85d.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/4b75b3b9464ad1389e13d65911781ada4dda3f47.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e54cfc1edae4997920e5db8145edeb377af94fc1.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/><br/>In addition to the price cut, the incendiary grenade has gotten a bit of a makeover with a new visual treatment for its explosion and flames, and reduced spread and duration. <br/><br/>And in other gameplay news, Vertigo's A-site has gotten some significant changes--it's now the site featured in Wingman matches, so check it out.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/955406bdcb60dba4a59ce0926fdd180946b7d9bb.png"/><br/><br/>Calling all Kilowatt Collection fans! Now, when you open a Kilowatt case with a key, you'll be given the option to rent the whole collection for a week (excluding the rare special item) instead of keeping a single item. You can play with the weapons as much as you like during that week, but they can't be modified by stickers or nametags.<br/><br/>Lots of other changes in today's update, including some quality of life improvements for demo playback, slightly smarter chickens, and a bit of spring cleaning--good news for fans of 'various bug fixes.'<br/><br/>Jump into a match and see what's new!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4177730135016204539</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Other Hand...</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4202497395512481609?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today's update includes a bunch of quality-of-life improvements that touch upon every part of the game, from maps to UI to gameplay. A few highlights are below, but check out the <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/730/view/4202497395513061959?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">release notes</span></a> to see what's new!<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2723ea38b9ba52592038731f15e5e9ba512be979.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/1a9b430c3ae10f5ec94a27d24f87187618d1919a.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/758e01194008b2d20797a378de390cdc24305cf9.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/>Lefties rejoice! Players can now redeploy their weapons, swapping between the left and right hand. You can set your preferred handedness in the settings menu and then switch hands temporarily mid-round with a key press (H on US Keyboards by default).<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/897b47892c65929ccd471ccff7d5aa65696eeb6f.png"/><br/>The buy menu has a few new tricks. To help you decide whether to buy or save, the top right of the buy menu now features the minimum amount of money you're guaranteed to have next round (thanks Kadomos). And at the bottom you'll find the new 'Dropped Weapons' panel, where you can see (and directly pick up) any weapons that you or teammates have dropped in the buy zone.<br/><br/><video autoplay="" height="auto" loop="" playsinline="" poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/f1462b7eefe16c70d61291b8676b1a404688da37.png?origin=" width="100%"><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e14db7419e60d31e09ed7d199683561d061bbc17.mp4?origin=" type="video/mp4"/><source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/ce366b2eaaf9211f367b50eec46533f8f99ba207.webm?origin=" type="video/webm"/></video><br/>There are several more HUD/UI changes in today's update. For those of you who have memorized a library of grenade line-ups, a line-up reticle will appear shortly after you pull the pin (you can even customize the delay for each grenade type). And if you've had trouble navigating through smoke, set a Radar Map Alternate Zoom and add a Toggle Radar Zoom key binding, which will let you switch between zoom levels during a round.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/ac9e7e5f1f6386cfec4de86e771a6fdc7206471c.png"/><br/>We've updated the Active Duty map pool (for both Premier and competitions), removing Overpass and bringing back Dust II. And there are changes to many other maps, including significant changes to Inferno.<br/><br/>Jump right into a match and see what's new, or practice with your friends--practice matches and workshop maps can now be launched with members of your party.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4202497395512481609</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copenhagen Major Champions</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4185606994270578198?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/75c3204fcb2874385f7c3e1dafeb00003b76502e.png"/><br/>Congratulations to Natus Vincere, the first CS2 Major Champions!<br/><br/>Playing in front of a sold-out arena and with over 1.8 million viewers watching around the world, NAVI and FaZe met in the Grand Final of one of the most hotly-contested Counter-Strike Majors of all time. Trading map wins in Ancient and Mirage, the teams moved to Inferno for the decider. There, b1t, jL, Aleksib, iM, and w0nderful put on a dominating performance to earn the trophy and title of Major Champions.<br/><br/>To celebrate their achievement, the Copenhagen 2024 Major Champions Capsule is now available for purchase. The capsule features autographs for each member of the winning team in paper, glitter, holo, and gold. 50% of the proceeds go to the players and organizations.<br/><br/>And with that, the Copenhagen Major has come to a close. See you next time in Shanghai!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4185606994270578198</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Championship Sunday in Copenhagen</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4167591962341209737?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d127fb6e4685f88d2921a5735ccba009dc2ff68d.png"/><br/>The Semifinals of the Copenhagen Major featured four titans of Counter-Strike; FaZe Clan versus Team Vitality and Natus Vincere versus G2 Esports.<br/> <br/>And the Semifinalists delivered! Both matchups required all three maps to determine a winner, and when the dust settled FaZe Clan and Natus Vincere were left standing. They will go head-to-head in the Grand Finals of Counter-Strike 2’s first Major Championship.<br/><br/>Championship Sunday begins with the Showmatch, beginning at 18:15 CET. The Grand Finals begin at 20:00 CET.<br/><br/>As the Major comes to a close there’s still time to support your favorite teams and players. Tournament items are available in-game, with 50% of the proceeds going to the players, teams, and organizations participating in the PGL Copenhagen Major. <br/><br/>See you Sunday!<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4167591962341209737</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
