<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Counter-Strike 2 - News (English)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml</link>
    <description>Counter-Strike 2 News Feed</description>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:33:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Copenhagen Playoffs and Pick’Ems</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4104540932633328367?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/b80e4de648288b7a193fb2218f6c6c6b348fa18a.png"/><br/>The Elimination Stage of the PGL Copenhagen Major has concluded, leaving eight teams to compete for Counter-Strike 2’s first Major Championship.<br/><br/>Congratulations to Team Spirit and MOUZ who advanced unbeaten, finishing with a perfect 3-0 record. Eternal Fire, Cloud9, and Team Vitality each went 3-1, and Natus Vincere, G2 Esports, and FaZe Clan went the distance, needing all five matches to advance with 3-2 records.<br/><br/>Playoff matches begin Thursday, March 28th from Royal Arena in Copenhagen, Denmark. Predictions for the Pick’Em Challenge are due before the first Playoff match begins, so lock in your picks now!<br/><br/>And don’t forget, team and player stickers are available now, with 50% of the proceeds going to the players, teams, and organizations participating in the PGL Copenhagen Major.<br/><br/>Good luck and have fun!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4104540932633328367</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGL Copenhagen 2024: Stickers!</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4104540932612285123?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The opening stage of the PGL Copenhagen Major has come to a close and storylines are rapidly developing. New rosters are rising to the occasion. Seasoned teams are reaching peak form at the perfect time. Asia and the Americas have come roaring back to life. Who will reach the playoffs? Tune in to the Elimination stage and find out!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d58744721b2c90bc58597bd0aeee173411b2c185.png"/><br/>If you've been looking for a way to show your support for your favorite teams, now is your chance. Team and Player Autograph sticker capsules are now available for purchase in the Copenhagen Major hub. You'll find all of the players and teams at the Major, split into capsules featuring paper, glitter, holo, and gold stickers. 50% of the proceeds go to the players and organizations participating in the Major.<br/><br/>For those of you playing the Pick'Em Challenge, don't forget to set your picks before the first Elimination stage matches!<br/><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4104540932612285123</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGL Copenhagen 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/6727887174668178386?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In December, hundreds of teams from around the world began their long journey to the first Counter-Strike 2 Major. Fighting through open, closed, and regional qualifiers--now only 24 remain. Tune in to the PGL Copenhagen Major on March 17th and watch the best Counter-Strike teams in the world battle for the title of Major Champion!<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/928b9520fe984786a92fbffb671023a42770d990.png"/><br/>Today we're shipping the all-new Copenhagen Major Hub, where you can find the Pick'Em Challenge, the Copenhagen 2024 Viewer Pass, Souvenirs, and (coming soon) Team and Player stickers. 50% of the proceeds from tournament items are shared with players and organizations.<br/><br/>Playing the Pick'Em Challenge with an active pass will give you a chance to upgrade your Copenhagen 2024 Coin and earn extra Souvenir Packages. You'll also show up on the Active Pass Leaderboard, where you can compare your Pick'Em Challenge performance to your friends.<br/><br/><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/e819d0a262182a891fcd7e8970f43e65b6072106.png"/><br/>In the past, you needed an active pass to play the Pick'Em game. No more! Now, everyone with Prime status can place their picks for free. However, to complete challenges and earn rewards from each event stage, you'll have to activate your pass before the stage begins.<br/><br/>So place your picks and get ready to cheer for your favorite teams. The PGL Copenhagen 2024 Major is almost here!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6727887174668178386</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Call to Arms</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4064004264605245458?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armsrace?snr=" tabindex="0"><span><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/aaae97dfe5530d92066a520ee5f83b233e926a0b.png"/></span></a><br/>Arms Race has returned! Grab your guns and brace yourself for a chaotic race to the top. Get two kills with each weapon to reach the final stage, or steal your opponents’ progress with your knife (or now with the Zeus)! Work your way up to the knife stage and earn the final kill to secure the win.<br/><br/>There's a lot more shipping today, from custom sticker placement to new content to gameplay updates. Click <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armsrace?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">here</span></a> to learn more!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4064004264605245458</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 Service Medal</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/6107508076983703492?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/6eba6fdad2eeb08061c08631ae1ebe7e14099427.png"/><br/><br/>Celebrate your time in CS2 with the all-new 2024 Service Medal, available starting January 1st!<br/><br/>To get your service medal, earn XP by playing in official game modes and rank up your CS2 Profile. When you reach Global General (Rank 40), you'll have the option to reset your Profile Rank and earn (or upgrade) a 2024 Service Medal. The medal is an inspectable display item you can show off wherever your avatar is shown.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6107508076983703492</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Maps Workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3787024475483064536?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/9b5fa738bb8617b7799066bedc75c1ab47ce6b23.png"/><br/>The Maps workshop is now open for business.<br/><br/>Community map makers can start uploading their maps to the workshop, and community servers can host those maps. If you'd like to try some workshop maps offline, subscribe to them on the workshop and head to the Play menu.<br/><br/>There are a bunch of other workshop tool updates today, along with a host of other fixes and adjustments to CS2. Check out the notes, play some matches, and keep that feedback coming!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3787024475483064536</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome Home</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3747614808335282785?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/8d881c9e69922ab988c6304052979d16bc920346.png"/><br/>Counter-Strike 2 is here.<br/><br/>Come take a look around. Counter-Strike 2 is the largest technical leap forward in Counter-Strike's history, supporting new features today and updates for years to come.<br/><br/>If you're a returning player you'll find your favorite maps and matchmaking modes right where you left them, along with a revamped Premier mode where you can establish your all-new CS Rating. Rise through the ranks and see where you stand on global and regional leaderboards.<br/><br/>For new players, learn the basics with some offline training and jump into Casual and Deathmatch to hone your skills. Once you've unlocked Competitive matchmaking you'll be off to the races.<br/><br/>Grab your friends, and come join millions of players around the world. Welcome to Counter-Strike 2.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3747614808335282785</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Time is Now</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3644028846252008595?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today we’re updating the CS2 Limited Test with a new map (Inferno!) and the all new CS Rating. <br/><br/>Your CS Rating is a visible measurement of your Counter-Strike performance, and it will determine where you stand on global and regional leaderboards. To get your CS Rating, play matches in the updated Premier mode (our Active Duty Pick-Ban competitive mode) either on your own or with your friends.<br/><br/><iframe allowfullscreen="" frameborder="0" height="748" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s6BNHro0vSg;full" style="width: 748px; height: 420px;" width="748"></iframe><br/><br/>Additionally, today we’re starting the process of inviting as many eligible players as possible to the Limited Test. To be eligible for a CS2 Limited Test invite players must have CS:GO Prime status, an active official competitive matchmaking Skill Group, and play majority of their official matchmaking games in one of the regions where the Limited Test is available.<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">Saving Time</div>Over the past decade, we’ve shipped updates to the economy and weapon balance to trim the fat and reduce the number of uncontested rounds in a match of CS.<br/><br/>Because of these changes, exciting competitive matches can be resolved with fewer rounds. And shorter matches mean players can play more, and more often. So with CS2, we’re moving to a maximum of 24 rounds in regulation time (with a 6 round overtime in case of a tie) for Premier, Competitive, and the Majors.<br/><br/>We expect the structure and flow of matches to evolve over time as the community adapts. And we’re excited to see where they go next.<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3644028846252008595</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Level Playing Field</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3677802763035982969?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counter-Strike is at its best when teams compete on a level playing field and when ability is the only limit to their success. <br/><br/>Over the past few years, we’ve seen professional Counter-Strike drift away from that ideal. The ecosystem has become gradually less open, with access to the highest levels of competition increasingly gated by business relationships. <br/><br/>We think that Counter-Strike should be an open sport. So we’re going to add new requirements to running large-scale competitive events. The finer details are still in progress, but here are the broad strokes:<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Tournament organizers will no longer have unique business relationships or other conflicts of interest with teams that participate in their events. <br/><br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Invitations to all tournaments will use our ranking system (detailed <a class="Focusable" href="https://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/?u=https%3A%2F%2Fgithub.com%2FValveSoftware%2Fcounter-strike%2Ftree%2Fmain%2Fregional_standings" rel="noopener nofollow" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="github.com">here</span></a>), or otherwise be determined by open qualifiers. <br/><br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Any compensation for participating teams—prize pool or otherwise—will be made public and will be driven by objective criteria that can be inspected by the community. <br/></li></ul>Since tournament organizers have existing long term commitments, these requirements will take effect as of 2025. There will be some rough edges to the transition, but we’re committed to the long-term health of Counter-Strike as a sport and are looking forward to its bright and open future.<br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3677802763035982969</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Wheel</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3702568031467132888?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/bb624914b5d1b52fcb1c862dedb11d8d42bf7793.png"/>Today we're shipping the first major update to the CS2 Limited Test. You can check out the <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/730/view/3702568031467145905?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">release notes</span></a> to see what's new, but here are some of the big changes in today's update:<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">New Loadout and Buy Menu</div><br/>Head to the loadout to customize the weapons you take into battle! Make your choices for the T and CT sides with four pistols, five mid-range weapons (SMGs and Heavy), and five rifles (yes, you can bring both M4's). Just drag and drop to adjust your buy menu however you see fit.<br/><br/>The buy menu has gotten a few extra upgrades, including a refund option for any weapons you purchased in the round and haven't used yet, and indicators to help you track what your teammates are carrying.<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">Workshop Tools</div><br/>The Limited Test now also includes all-new Counter-Strike 2 Workshop Tools, which can be enabled and downloaded from the in-game settings menu. These tools will allow community contributors to create weapon finishes, stickers, and maps.<br/><br/>There's much more in today's update, from smoke grenade adjustments to input and animation. Jump into the Limited Test and send your feedback to cs2team [at] valvesoftware [dot] com (make sure to include CS2LT in your title).]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3702568031467132888</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Vitality - Major Champions!</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3702568031445748803?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/csgoparis2023?snr=" tabindex="0"><span><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/f172d2084850b4719a2332c9c98ce030f8ce88c7.png"/></span></a><br/><br/>Congratulations to Team Vitality, champions of the BLAST.TV Paris Major! They defeated GamerLegion and completed a dominating performance, sailing through the event without losing a single map. <br/><br/>Today we are releasing the Paris 2023 Champions Autograph Capsule, featuring autographs from apEX, dupreeh, Magisk, Spinx, and ZywOo. Celebrate the champions in style, with paper, glitter, holo, and gold player autograph stickers!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3702568031445748803</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Finale</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3686804163583320073?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/4cd2b3130a0c580dbfc5c6b8f87a61896fae75e4.png"/><br/><br/>The BLAST.tv Paris Major began with 24 teams and 2 finalists remain: GamerLegion and Team Vitality. <br/><br/>The Champions Stage saw GamerLegion defeat Monte 2-0 and Heroic 2-1 on their path to the Grand Finals. <br/><br/>In front of a home crowd Team Vitality bested Into the Breach and Apeks 2-0 on consecutive days. The Grand Finals of the last CS:GO Major take place tomorrow, May 21st, from Accor Arena in Paris.<br/><br/>Team items are available <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/csgoparis2023?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">here</span></a> with 50% of the proceeds going to teams and organizations taking part in the Major.<br/><br/>Good luck to the grand finalists!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3686804163583320073</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On to the Finals</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/5448836977171499668?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/14b184db38811db48b84d3fd439f8caf501aec41.png"/><br/><br/>The Legends Stage of the BLAST.tv Paris Major has concluded and the Champions Stage is set. The following teams will compete to become Major Champions of the final CS:GO Major:<br/><br/><span class="Bold">3-0:</span><br/>Heroic<br/>Vitality<br/><br/><span class="Bold">3-1:</span><br/>GamerLegion<br/>Monte<br/>Team Liquid<br/><br/><span class="Bold">3-2:</span><br/>Apeks<br/>FaZe<br/>Into the Breach<br/><br/>The Quarterfinals begin Thursday, May 18th, at 6:00pm Paris time GMT+2. The conclusion of the Legends Stage means Pick'Ems are now open for the Champions Stage.<br/><br/>Team items are available <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/csgoparis2023?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">here</span></a> with 50% of the proceeds going to teams and organizations taking part in the Major.<br/><br/>Good luck to the final 8 teams!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5448836977171499668</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enter The Legends</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/5448836977153818924?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/01a596a210639b94aaf175af53b9c5b8db2ca38f.png"/><br/>The Challengers Stage of the BLAST.tv Paris Major has concluded and 8 teams have advanced to the Legends Stage.<br/><br/><span class="Bold">3-0:</span><br/>ENCE<br/>G2<br/><br/><span class="Bold">3-1:</span><br/>Apeks<br/>FaZe<br/>Ninjas in Pyjamas<br/><br/><span class="Bold">3-2:</span><br/>GamerLegion<br/>Monte<br/>Team Liquid<br/><br/>The Legends Stage begins May 13th and Pick'Ems are now open. <br/><br/>Team items are available <a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/csgoparis2023?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">here</span></a> with 50% of the proceeds going to teams and organizations taking part in the Major.<br/><br/>Good luck to the 16 remaining teams!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5448836977153818924</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Paris 2023 Major</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/3717202192664258501?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/csgoparis2023?snr=" tabindex="0"><span><img src="https://cdn.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/steamcommunity/public/images/clans/3381077/92f2b149a5b2ed9052397c8b518b7a8807d8cf3b.png"/></span></a><br/><a class="Focusable" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/csgoparis2023?snr=" tabindex="0"><span data-tooltip-text="store.steampowered.com">The BLAST.TV Paris Major</span></a> begins May 8th. Who will become the champion of CS:GO's final Major?<br/><br/>Show your support for all of the teams and players with team stickers, player autographs, and the Paris 2023 Viewer Pass, all available for purchase now! 50% of the proceeds go to the players, teams, and organizations taking part in the Major.<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">The Paris 2023 Viewer Pass</div><br/>With a Paris 2023 Viewer Pass, you'll receive an upgradable Paris 2023 Event Coin, access to the Pick'em Challenge, team graffiti, Steam.tv flair, and exclusive access to Paris 2023 Souvenir Packages.<br/><br/>Each time you upgrade your Paris 2023 Event Coin, you'll receive a Souvenir Token that can be redeemed for a Souvenir Package from the match of your choice. Souvenirs feature gold stickers of the teams and map of the match you selected.<br/><br/>You can earn up to three Souvenir Tokens by playing the Pick'em Challenge, but if you'd like more, purchase the 'Viewer Pass +3' and you'll get three Souvenir Tokens right away. You can also purchase as many Souvenir Tokens as you like once you've activated your Paris 2023 Viewer Pass.<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Header3_2q6Vr BB_Header3">Team and Player Capsules</div><br/>Looking for your favorite Team or Player? Check out the Team and Player Autograph capsules, featuring paper, glitter, holo, and gold stickers. And shortly after the Grand Final concludes, Champions Autograph Capsules (feature autographs of players on the winning team) will be available for purchase.<br/><br/>The Major is just days away. Activate your Viewer Pass, make your picks, and get ready for the best teams in the game to make CS:GO history.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3717202192664258501</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
