<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Counter-Strike 2 - News (English)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml</link>
    <description>Counter-Strike 2 News Feed</description>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <image>
      <url>https://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/apps/csgo/images/csgo_react/global/cs2_icon_color_512x512.png</url>
      <title>Counter-Strike 2 - News (English)</title>
      <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/news-feed-en.xml</link>
    </image>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 01:34:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Starladder Budapest Major 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/578276333072682038</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>As 2025 comes to an end, the <a rel="nofollow" href="https://major.starladder.com/en/news/starladder-to-host-2025-cs2-major-in-budapest-s-20-000-seat-mvm-dome">StarLadder Budpest Major 2025</a> is set to begin. Join us as the first stage begins on Monday, November 24th!</p><p></p><p>All three stages of the StarLadder Budapest Major will be played in front of live crowds at MTK Sportpark, and for the first time at a Counter-Strike Major, the Grand Finals will be best of five. Now more than ever, the Major Champions will need to prove their quality by winning three maps in the Active Duty Map Pool.</p><p></p><h2>Make Your Picks</h2><p>You can begin supporting your favorite teams participating in the Major with the Budapest 2025 Viewer Pass.</p><p></p><p><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/15969ca6f557f569d64c5842d14cb0f9956959e9.png"/></p><p>Your activated Budapest 2025 Viewer Pass includes a coin that can be upgraded by playing the Pick&#39;Em challenge. Pass holders gain access to unlimited team graffiti for the duration of the event and can earn and purchase Souvenir Tokens, which can be redeemed for a Souvenir from the match of your choice.</p><p></p><p><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/efa11c895cae00d15d7aecc49ed2b29d48d4b898.png"/></p><p>And back by popular demand, Playoff Souvenirs for the StarLadder Budapest Major come with Souvenir Charms, featuring highlights from the match! </p><p></p><h2>Get Your Stickers</h2><p>With the release of the Viewer Pass and Pick&#39;Em Challenge, we are also releasing StarLadder Budapest Major tournament stickers, featuring logos of every team and signatures of every player participating in the Major. </p><p><br /><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c42b08ddad56444ff7eebb84c68a9b7f25573f79.png"/></p><h2>Slab Your Stickers</h2><p>
            <video controls poster="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/ca2c415dbeb92d7a7e6a01851f59a117553ae8de.png">
                <source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/75e8fef8d0e0846f0dfa4e392ddfef0f0ab559e7.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/381d49320e03c6cfb3fbfa53b3223f4a4b2c435d.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            </p><p></p><p>Not ready to apply your favorite sticker? We got you! Today we are introducing Sticker Slabs<strong>—</strong>charms that let you show off a sticker with no commitment. Later, just break the slab to return the sticker to your inventory.</p>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">578276333072682038</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 01:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing TrueView</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/578276333072678918</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Today we&#39;re adding a new feature to demo playback called <em>TrueView</em>. With TrueView, demo playback will match the player&#39;s original experience much more closely.</p><p>Previously, demo playback showed the server&#39;s view of the world, without accounting for network latency. This could be confusing because shots would hit that didn&#39;t look like they should have, and vice versa. </p><p>TrueView provides a more accurate representation of the observed player&#39;s experience by re-running their <a rel="nofollow" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Client-side_prediction"><em>client-side prediction</em></a>.</p><p>The video below shows the difference between the old demo playback and the same playback with TrueView.</p><p>
            <video controls poster="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/62030ce08e8f12c926a4f6d935273d4dd68eb0bb.jpg">
                <source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/9ca1d515aebe8c11b94bcd3dd1ee9f28c02f0909.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/9a8ab6de516a3c52f5d76f2174fd45976d8203b2.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            </p><p>A few caveats:</p><ul><li><p>By default, TrueView is deactivated when the version of the game you are using to view the demo does not match the version of the game used to record the demo.</p></li><li><p>Even with TrueView active, there may still be some differences between what you see in the demo and what the player originally saw (especially with slow-motion playback). For example, damage effects will have different timing during demo playback due to the way CPU and GPU work are pipelined.</p></li><li><p>In addition to performing clientside prediction of the observed player, TrueView will also perform Damage Prediction on enemies, if Damage Prediction was used by the observed player at the time. </p></li></ul><p></p><p>Additionally, we&#39;re shipping movement changes that we made available last week in a beta branch. All that and more and today&#39;s update!</p>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">578276333072678918</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Retakes</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/516350567072661952</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p></p><p><img src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/aae1ceb26e12464542579430a2436c8348461b5c.png"/></p><p>The bomb has been planted and you&#39;re running out of time. It&#39;s the return of retakes! </p><p>In this classic game mode, each round drops you in to a fast-paced 4v3 after-plant scenario. Select your loadout card each round, check the map to coordinate with your teammates, and use your resources wisely to defuse (or defend) the planted bomb.</p><p>The clock is ticking, what are you waiting for? Jump into a retakes server now!</p>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">516350567072661952</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 23:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Maps, Charms, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/498333631688738072</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Let&#39;s get right into it. Today&#39;s update features new Wingman and Competitive community maps, along with brand new charms (including community designs), stickers, and more.</p><p></p><h3>Community Maps</h3><p>
            <video controls poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/61b420dee3aff1796ba385d7405396b5047deb15.png">
                <source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/c5ab133e75f3b6b2c822652b91d16dfffad9bdd1.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/1328ecdd3aff19f14078872e0b8eea7e24e615f8.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            From the mines of Golden to the moving train in Transit, we&#39;ve got four new Community maps for you to check out. Golden and Palacio have been added to Competitive, Casual, and Deathmatch modes, and Rooftop and Transit have been added to Wingman.</p><p></p><h3>New Armory Content</h3><p>
            <video controls poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/1b2f71d055a5b73ec263d88ebf1cd5c7108aa1da.png">
                <source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/0316226665da792bf99752da24c6869c5bb26496.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/76714b20b536928194ade6f5237890cf2a25239d.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            It&#39;s a lil&#39; HE grenade&#8230; for your gun. It doesn&#39;t explode, but it sure is <em>charming</em>. Introducing the all new Dr. Boom Charms, now available in the Armory.</p><p></p><p>
            <video controls poster="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/7490b11599e34e5b309e1680892689cde14a69eb.png">
                <source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/c2e64c689b7e6aa8ea134de7c06b6e0cea790a4d.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/9b6ecf851f93202f7c7e3a1a6c1e80fd29e71239.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            A few months ago we added charms to the workshop, and you responded. For some insight into the creative and occasionally twisted minds of the CS2 community, check out the Missing Link Community Charms in the Armory.</p><p></p><p><img src="{STEAM_CLAN_IMAGE}/3381077/9a588a3121139f437497d4a279e279f29f10998f.png"/></p><p>Speaking of community designs, the Armory now features two brand new sticker collections, including the return of Sugarface!</p>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">498333631688738072</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Off</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/514095143786120351</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hear that? It&#39;s the sound of a new update in CS2&#8230; and your grenades, which now have unique higher-fidelity sounds for draw, inspect, pin-pull, and throw. For community map makers, there&#39;s a new scripting system available along with some examples for you to check out. All that and more in today&#39;s update!<br /><br /><h3>Spectator Loadout</h3><br /><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/b26902d359f70916d03ac20ffeb0f952c0560969.png"/><br />Finally, a reason to be happy your teammates are dead. While you&#39;re busy clutching, your teammates can peek at your full loadout, inspect your weapons, and possibly offer you unsolicited fashion advice. Stay alive, and show off the best of your collection!<br /><br /><h3>Genesis Collection</h3><br /><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/e2105aa13baf7a235ad428edf1471e827d546ea6.png"/><br />Introducing the Genesis Collection, featuring 17 finishes from community contributors. Genesis Collection items can be accessed via Genesis Uplink Terminals, which are available as a weekly drop.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/5a7f29b354db4258a2130d67838cc2ca6f5a11cf.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/483d33d1546dc4e7fe4a23e45b0e78fd142f32a6.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/8e8c12b0f0150152f475d05d046a89b8bb30be8c.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/1ff654371af827dd4dfa259d3902405ea3ec520c.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/5263d234a66f96aac942fd1cd3ad3cc1874af91e.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c12c4e59cbd20664e88cb1d860a47f1b1601dc6e.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2bcd68852e6364af93dbf6bf77d554ad83499686.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/5fb454102e22de082a700f492805a2807f9795a9.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/a301600c1f6cccfb26938e5a93472ad6b92afd24.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/38d17f84139d1fdc22c949e23570cab8206fedad.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/af57c9cafb20b16244760bc1a301421b433e1e36.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/8e495aeddb588a58b05edef25fe3be47f8f1b8bb.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c745181dbb81667ceee7960d5eaa4f8e3940512c.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/bdea0bb48555f739f13d0a92474d9fde6c53d002.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c94951b3977daf1856293a94ef35e2b5ff68e2f7.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/5bf6d932c3de247426d941ba8adbea889052280e.png"/><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/38b5ca9d1e0ada2117be9d890dc903d7462f58e8.png"/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">514095143786120351</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tonight's Forecast: Rain-cient</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/657081807721726187</link>
      <description><![CDATA[
            <video controls poster="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/733ba62744ceed1830313e5f1e76202a3a438d89.png">
                <source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/cde1a6abee69ded5d36a86cfde56d34c40a236b8.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2c16675dfd832ded0baf8f60ce9a97e5e984661e.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            <br />It&#39;s a brand new day (and night) in CS2&#39;s tropical maps. Ancient and Shoots have gotten visual upgrades, and now have nighttime versions. The nighttime version of Ancient is only available in Casual and Deathmatch.<br /><br />
            <video controls poster="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/ea656d70b40c673bfbdd62fc7ba8ef2b08753b0a.png">
                <source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d19e820cd2e82c01022e1caa608a9ce9fd804d80.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/7de0428872115c68522389cd94c79e4d829996ad.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            <br /><br /><hr /><br />Today we are releasing the Deluge Music Kit Box, featuring music kits from Adam Beyer, Ghost, HEALTH, James and the Cold Gun, Jonathan Young, Juelz, Killer Mike, PVRIS, Selective Response, and Tigercub.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/1813e20b58e7ddf9d97065e14fcb2bbaa5158c5f.png"/><br />We&#39;re also refreshing the Limited Time item in the Armory&ndash;the M4A1-S | Solitude is now available.<br /><br />
            <video controls poster="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/d951a0609cf9a5cabe13211646f2e452bae1d751.png">
                <source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/3d9a3b13b8c757555eef6f4dbd9f6f1c60c9d626.mp4" type="video/mp4">
<source src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/1ae824f1d3f2ba28ce1a473a43bd13d3e5ee266a.webm" type="video/webm">
            </video>
            <br />Ready to check out some night maps? Grab a cup of coffee and go go go! <br /><br />Release Notes for today can be found <a rel="nofollow" href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/730/view/657081807721726196">here</a>.]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">657081807721726187</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season Two: Episode One</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529852487375519751</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/f780ca0f8f1f5561b4f72030672ed657382ecd9a.png"/><br />Premier Season Three begins today!<br /><br />It&#39;s time to start working toward your Season Three Medal. As before, the color of your medal will correspond to the highest CS Rating achieved during the season, and the bars will reflect your total wins, with one bar for every 25 (up to five bars). To be eligible for a medal, you&#39;ll need an account in good standing, 25 Premier match wins, and an active CSR at the end of the season.<br /><br /><h3>New for Season 3 </h3><br />With the new season comes an update to the Active Duty Map Pool: Overpass is back in, and Anubis is out.<br /><br />There are a few gameplay changes with Season Three. Fire from the incendiary grenade now spreads faster, occupying space rapidly to counter rushing Ts. The MP9 has gotten a bit of a nerf, with a harder to control spray and substantially less jumping accuracy. There&#39;s also a change to the CT economy: win or lose, CTs now receive a shared team award for each T eliminated in the round, so the more you win and the closer you keep your losses, the more you&#39;ll have to spend.<br /><br /><h3>Trade Protected Items</h3><br />Today we are introducing a new feature to help keep your Counter-Strike items secure. In the unlikely event that you lose control of your account or were the target of a scam by a bad actor, you may reverse all Counter-Strike item trades from the last 7 days. <br /><br />Obviously we hope you&#39;ll never need it, but you can review your recent trades and find the trade reversal feature on the Trade History page on your Steam Account. For more information about what happens when trades are reversed, visit the <a rel="nofollow" href="https://help.steampowered.com/en/faqs/view/365F-4BEE-2AE2-7BDD">FAQ</a>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529852487375519751</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAST.tv Austin Major Champions</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529850584204838951</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images//3381077/295fc91153ac46320f142edffbd45c4e5b31c394.png"/><br />Over four days, the Moody Center in Austin, Texas hosted Team Vitality&#39;s coronation as the best Counter-Strike team on the planet.<br /><br />Facing The MongolZ in the Grand Finals, Team Vitality lost the opening map 13:5, then stormed back on the next two, winning 13:4 on Dust II and 13:6 on Inferno to win the BLAST.tv Austin Major and the organization&#39;s second Major Championship.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/13f607e38001ed765a63729028036855b884c715.png"/><br />To celebrate, today we are releasing the Major Champions Capsule, featuring Paper, Foil, Holo, and Gold stickers autographed by one of the Champions from Team Vitality. <br /><br />And for the first time, we are introducing Souvenir Charms. Each Playoff Stage Souvenir comes with a Souvenir Charm that contains a highlight from the match. <br /><br />Finally, Season Two of Premier ends on July 14th. To receive your Premier Season Two Medal, you must have 25 Season Two Premier wins and a visible CSR when the Season concludes.<br /><br />See you soon for Premier Season Three!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529850584204838951</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 22:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capture the Moment</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529848048073835651</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The BLAST.tv Austin Major is fast approaching! <br /><br />Activate your Austin 2025 Viewer Pass and set your Pick&#39;Ems before the first matches start, and you&#39;ll be well on your way to upgrading your Challenge Coin and earning Souvenir Tokens. Speaking of which&#8230;<br /><br /><h3>Souvenir Highlight Packages</h3><br /><br />Just like previous Majors, you&#39;ll have the opportunity to claim a memento from the match of your choice. But this time, if you choose a <strong>playoff match</strong>, you&#39;ll receive an <em>all new</em> Souvenir Highlight Package.<br /><br />Available exclusively for playoff stage matches, Souvenir Highlight Packages contain a souvenir weapon with an attached charm that features a video highlight from the playoff map you selected. Your weapon&#39;s description will include information about the highlight, and you can view the attached clip in your CS2 inventory, in Steam, or while spectating a teammate in-match.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/43fc8779bd35f9f8ef4244d4fa7581aea714a322.png"/><br />We&#39;re excited for everyone to get their chance to pick up a playoffs-exclusive Souvenir Highlight Package, but they will take some time to put together. So stay tuned—Souvenir Highlight Packages will be redeemable shortly after the Major comes to a close!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529848048073835651</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 23:09:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAST.TV Austin Major 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529847413482979949</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Like a dust storm on the horizon, the <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blast.tv/cs/austin-major-2025">BLAST.TV Austin Major</a> is fast approaching. Join us June 3rd as the first stage of the major gets underway!<br /><br /><h2>Pick&#39;Em and Stick&#39;Em</h2><br />Featuring more teams than ever before, this Major promises to be the most competitive yet. And you can start supporting your favorite teams today with the Austin 2025 Viewer Pass!<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/35cdb694da776a40377c9c4a2fa29ebf07d38f5d.png"/><br />Your activated Austin 2025 Viewer Pass includes a coin that you can upgrade by playing the Pick&#39;Em challenge, along with unlimited team graffiti for the duration of the event so you can show your support everywhere you play. You&#39;ll also have the opportunity to earn (and purchase) Souvenir Tokens, redeemable for a memento from the match of your choice. <br /><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/b9ccae936af6a1bf8ef076140595e8cec37c7a81.png"/><br />Along with the Viewer Pass and Pick&#39;Em Challenge, today we&#39;re releasing tournament stickers featuring the logos of every participating team and the autograph of every participating player. With a bit of Texas flair, Austin Major stickers can be found in a variety of finishes so you can find the perfect look for your collection. <br /><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/85a9d07d5ef8006de47176a7be56cafc64ac14e3.png"/><br />So mark your calendar, dust off your boots, and join us in Austin for Counter-Strike&#39;s biggest Major yet!<br /><br /><h2>Stick to Your Guns</h2><br /><br />But that&#39;s not all!<br /><br />We&#39;ve partnered with Games Workshop to celebrate the Warhammer Skulls 2025 event by releasing four Warhammer 40,000-themed sticker capsules.<br /><br />Themed after Warhammer 40,000 decal sheets, you&#39;ll find the Warhammer 40,000 Adeptus Astartes, Traitor Astartes, Imperium, and Xenos Sticker Capsules in-game now!<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/edb17546cd7f439b4baab2a311a94c5557c9eafc.png"/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529847413482979949</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 00:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mission Possible</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529846144626327818</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today&#39;s update includes several community maps, a rearranging of casual and deathmatch map groups, and the introduction of weekly missions!<br /><br /><h3>Weekly Missions</h3><br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c33643703076e28d5979c51ed2bcef6c8c40b106.png"/><br /><br />Your mission, should you choose to accept it, can be completed for bonus XP. Each week you&#39;ll get a new mission, and you can access your mission in the Main Menu and in the Play Menu.<br /><br /><h3>Community Maps</h3><br /><br />Today we welcome a host of new community maps: Jura, Grail and Agency have been added to Competitive, Casual, and Deathmatch modes, and Dogtown and Brewery have been added to Wingman. And it&#39;s easier than ever to play community maps—Jura, Grail, and Agency can be found in the new Community Map Group.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/533154f720195f2032a302a5fed0a785dafbfb21.png"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/0521b3dbaf187b3ff154d0efa5e23c3dd829943b.png"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/342e88dbbef797238e60a492e95eb47e82687e8f.png"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/afa0f29d86f969c4e8f7cf3ab3f00ebc5e84750e.png"/><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/7d152e290ec0d02e1d47167682bfb60132411e96.png"/> <br /><br />All this and more (<a rel="nofollow" href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/730/view/529846144626327635">particularly for fans of binding keys to &quot;/&quot;</a>) in today&#39;s update, so jump into some community maps and see what&#39;s new!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529846144626327818</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 22:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Season's Greetings</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/520830071182721028</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Welcome to Premier Season Two. <br /><br />If you haven&#39;t heard the news, here&#39;s what&#39;s new in Season Two. Vertigo is out, Train is in, the M4A4 is more&#8230; A4-dable&#8230; and we&#39;ve tweaked the FAMAS. <br /><br />Season Two runs from now through the Austin Major, at which point players who meet the requirements will be awarded a Premier Season Two Medal. The color will correspond to your highest CS Rating achieved during the season, and the bars will reflect your total wins, with one bar for every 25—up to five bars.<br /><br />To earn your Premier Season Two Medal, you&#39;ll need an account in good standing, 25 Premier match wins, and an active CSR at the end of the season.<br /><br />Premier matchmaking is now open for business, so hit the queue and start racking up those wins!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">520830071182721028</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champions of Shanghai</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/529833471389991079</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/c832bcc989b6e03012fde727c077c846d245cb22.jpg"/><br />The Perfect World Shanghai Grand Final was one to remember. Team Spirit and FaZe Clan needed all three maps to determine a champion in front of an excited, sold-out crowd at the SPD Bank Oriental Sports Center.<br /><br />Down 12:5 on map 3, FaZe Clan battled back with 6 consecutive round wins—and some incredible clutches along the way—to force round 24. With the bomb planted and down to a 1v1, sh1ro&#39;s final kill earned Team Spirit their first Major Championship.<br /><br />Celebrate Team Spirit&#39;s win with the Major Champions Capsule, now available for purchase. The capsule features autographs from Team Spirit in paper, glitter, holo, and gold, and 50% of the proceeds go to the players and organizations.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/3ed2c31143f07013ef30373c1458adc84731c04d.png"/><br />With Shanghai in the books we look forward to the BLAST.tv Major in Austin, Texas. See you in June 2025!<br /><br /><h3>2025 Service Medal</h3><br /><img src="https://clan.cloudflare.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/7f0747f83da9da8ed752f3848e0ab17caf40de9d.png"/><br />Beginning January 1st, 2025 players can receive the newest Service Medal in-game. <br /><br />When you reach Global General (Rank 40) you&#39;ll have the option to reset your Profile Rank and earn (or upgrade) a 2025 Service Medal.<br /><br />Good luck and have fun!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">529833471389991079</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 01:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai 2024 Major</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4472732402493426409</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Counter-Strike Major has come to Shanghai.<br /><br />Over the past month, teams from around the world challenged the best in their region for their spot in the Major. Now the dust has settled and 24 teams remain&ndash;perennial favorites, seasoned veterans, and more than a few newcomers.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/f0f38a64ad92793e959eec2a45ff34098daf8f38.png"/><br />The Shanghai Major Hub is now open for business, complete with the Pick&#39;Em Challenge, the Shanghai 2024 Viewer Pass, Souvenirs, Graffiti, and Team and Player stickers. 50% of the proceeds from tournament items are shared with players and organizations.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/56dc2ad026cabb70fc939f0dfa95c9bf4227dce4.png"/><br />The Pick&#39;Em Challenge is free to play, but if you want to upgrade your Shanghai 2024 Coin (and earn extra Souvenir Packages), make sure to activate your Viewer Pass before the event begins. You can also compare your Pick&#39;Em performance to other friends with active passes on the Active Pass Leaderboard.<br /><br /><img src="https://clan.fastly.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/2a940af901af1afe7527f1fb2eb7c2e9e51d3e32.png"/><br />It&#39;s time to support your favorite teams. Place your picks, set your graffiti, mark your calendar and get ready, because the Shanghai Major is about to begin. May the best team win!]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4472732402493426409</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Armory</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/newsentry/4674264042200250912</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Today&#39;s update introduces the Armory, all new Weapon Charms, and a whole lot more. Click the image below for more details!<br /><a rel="nofollow" href="https://store.steampowered.com/sale/armory"><img src="https://clan.akamai.steamstatic.com/images/3381077/4f30364bf12221dd5c8db6fa9f113fee1e8b0641.png"/></a>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4674264042200250912</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 23:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
