<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Counter-Strike 2 - Updates (English)</title>
    <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/updates-feed-en.xml</link>
    <description>Counter-Strike 2 Updates Feed</description>
    <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/IceQ1337/CS-RSS-Feed/master/feeds/updates-feed-en.xml" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:38:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 4/16/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where bomb can sometimes disappear from the radar<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Allow scraping or removing stickers by selecting the sticker icons under the weapon<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Allow deleting empty storage units that have an assigned label<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed Workshop tools from crashing when compiling maps that contain instances<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2167658c7ed469cc3604d122f3ff91ec343932a7e04583d98b2465ee1b4a1a3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 4/2/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ COPENHAGEN 2024 MAJOR ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Congratulations to Natus Vincere for winning the PGL Copenhagen Major!<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> The Copenhagen 2024 Champions Autograph Capsule is now available for purchase in the Copenhagen 2024 Major Hub</li></ul><br/>[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed several cases of sticky collisions when jumping against surfaces<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed another threading bug that could lead to a frame rate hitch, especially if all CPUs were busy<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Purchased and traded Counter-Strike items will not be visible to other users who view your Steam Inventory for 10 days</li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb2b7dfda5fd59a3a4ecfa167f55d311d79444a38fd7181c95493ad3e81105aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 3/19/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ COPENHAGEN 2024 MAJOR ]<ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Elimination Stage Pick'Em Challenge is now active with 13 qualified teams (three more teams will qualify tomorrow). Elimination Stage picks can be updated and saved all the way until the first Elimination Stage matches begin<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Added a reminder for players who purchased their Copenhagen 2024 Viewer Pass that the pass must be activated in order to become eligible for the Copenhagen 2024 Coin Challenges<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Added a checkbox to show final Swiss standings in the Major Hub<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Added ability to preview souvenir packages from the Major Hub<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Various UI improvements in Copenhagen 2024 Major Hub<br/></li></ul><br/>[ MISC ]<ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a case when C4 could fall through the floor if dropped while planting<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Added a popup confirmation before launching Training Day from the Play menu<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3db24f2c5730bd06dc1c40afbe5ae619311e58793eec7b3a4b42c67213d1929</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 3/13/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[COPENHAGEN 2024 MAJOR]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> The Copenhagen Major Hub is now available. Visit the hub to purchase tournament items, play the Pick'Em Challenge and more.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Purchase a Copenhagen 2024 Viewer Pass to receive an upgradable Copenhagen 2024 Coin. With an active pass, you can upgrade your coin and earn extra souvenir packages by playing the Pick'Em Challenge. Additionally, you will show up on the Active Pass Leaderboard where you can compare your Pick'Em Challenge performance to your friends.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> All players with Prime status can place Pick'Em picks for free! However, to complete challenges and earn rewards from an event stage, you will have to activate a Viewer Pass before that stage begins.<br/></li></ul><br/>[GAMEPLAY]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Adjusted molotov fire to address a case where a player who could see through fire could not be seen by their opponent.<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13ddb524d658553ed79b1c7fca99b1b1ca7019fc1da4eda64bd6a4bcd386cc2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Note for 3/8/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a threading bug that could lead to a frame rate hitch, especially if all CPUs were busy.<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f5bdea9d23349753226618a79adf13a8cfdf72d6b5b775516a9bcc61bc3db18</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/28/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Spawn position is no longer randomly determined when a player reconnects to a server during freeze time. The spawn point sequence is now configured at the beginning of the map and is saved/restored from round backup files<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">In official matchmaking servers, players who disconnect and reconnect during freeze time will respawn in the spawn point they were assigned at the beginning of the round<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">On community servers, players who disconnect and reconnect during freeze time will be assigned one of the five spawn positions assigned to the team that round<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">When restoring from round backup files (which is recommended in tournament settings after disconnects/reconnects), players will spawn in the positions they were originally assigned at the beginning of that round<br/></li></ul></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where players would see a black screen after disconnecting and reconnecting multiple times during a technical timeout<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where players disconnecting and reconnecting to a competitive match would incorrectly interact with bot spawning algorithm<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some cases where MVP music would not play or would play over round end music<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug in Deathmatch where kills during warmup would count towards healthshot reward and Zeus score bonus<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed players jumping higher than normal when toggling low framerate<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed an instance of weapon switches sometimes being ignored by the server<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed smoke shadow rendering issues and improvements to perf<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where the game would crash on Linux while alt-tabbing<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some cases where a frame rate hitch would occur due to compiling shaders<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved behavior when user input does not arrive on the server in time due to packet loss or client frame rate issues<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted various music kit cues in NIGHTMODE Music Kit box (ISOxo, Knock2, and TWERL and Ekko &amp; Sidetrack)<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a case where some players in North America would always fail to accept a match on a server in Europe due to SDR choosing an invalid route<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Players who get kicked from official competitive servers for too many suicides will now be issued a competitive cooldown<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted the logic tracking player idle state to exclude round freezetime and timeout periods<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Chickens no longer interact with dropped weapons<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Sniper scope overlay no longer appears in tool viewports (such as Hammer)<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ MAPS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted spawn location priorities for Premier and Competitive game modes in Anubis, Inferno, Mirage, Nuke, Overpass, and Vertigo.</li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Inferno</div><br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed community reported gaps in map and Trike model<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Raised plywood at top of Banana to cover head visibility<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Smoothed ground movement in Banana and Bombsite A<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Raised Arch exit towards Mid (or "Raised arch in Arch")<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Removed bench at Arch near Library<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Removed construction cone at Underpass<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ WORKSHOP ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fix lightmaps being capped at 4k resolution in CS2 Workshop Tools<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Updated sticker inspect to support wear in 0.1 increments to match sticker scraping<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added roughness texture to foil stickers in the Item Editor<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Updated help system for new sticker features<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed126e0e1b964d548e2e4a16b649353764770c03689f6a45d39eee9f468a0283</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/16/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">50% throw-strength grenades are now guaranteed if both attack buttons are held long enough then released within a short time from each other<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed in-game bot avatar images not reloading correctly after pause menu was opened<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed behaviour of previous round button during demo playback<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed inability to clear a button binding in game settings<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved performance of telemetry display HUD element<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Normalized volume of NIGHTMODE music kits<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Stability improvements<br/></li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6c948cbdf671c58a5b734fd99adefa1630e4376b68fc0ed2a55b7af0ee2057c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/15/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ ANIMATION ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fix for animations when climbing ladders<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fix for menu agents wielding tasers<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fix for Kukri knife hold animation during team intro sequence<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ SPECTATING ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">spec_lock_to_accountid and spec_lock_to_current_player commands are now available for casters/observers<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">spec_player and spec_goto now works in CSTV and demo playback<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">tv_secure_bypass server setting now allows connecting HLAE observers to VAC secure CSTV servers<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ GAMEPLAY ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> In Deathmatch, the Zeus can be bought each life and will rebuy if not in random weapon mode<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> In Deathmatch, getting a second Zeus kill in the same life will earn double points<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> mp_modify_timeouts server-side command allows adding/subtracting a tactical timeout from CT/T team if backup file is restored or a team incorrectly took a tactical timeout instead of a technical timeout<br/></li></ul><br/><br/><br/>[ LOGGING ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Start of warmup and end of warmup will now produce a log message in the game server log<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Reported damage no longer has a rounding error when reported in the game server log<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved viewmodel animation smoothness when client framerates get low or unstable<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed issues with implementation of scancode-based key bindings. Bindings are now independent of input locales.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added performance diagnostic HUD element that can be configured in Game Settings menu ("Telemetry")<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Deleted cq_netgraph and cq_netgraph_problem_show_auto.  Instead, use cl_hud_telemetry_serverrecvmargin_graph_show.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fix for sometimes failing to connect to a local practice server without Steam connectivity<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug with Skill Group animation at the end of competitive matches<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed sniper scope performance hitch and adjusted visual treatment. <br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Various performance improvements<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ MAPS ]<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Vertigo:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed grenade clipping around AC unit at B-site<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed clipping of pillar at T-Start that would potentially allow bomb to be thrown into unreachable area<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Nuke:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted clipping around Vents entrance to prevent players' feet clipping through the vent geo<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved collision of sliding door meshes at Ramp<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Anubis:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added and removed a ladder near boost spot by T spawn<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a couple of spots where bomb could be thrown out of the map<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Overpass:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Clipping improvements<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some disappearing mesh<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2cf3e55e6b796699804bade2c8d7499fceccf16491c5929c2b3c11852327f8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/12/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Reconnecting to the game server will no longer get a player into a bad state.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Improved VOIP performance when running the game at very high framerates.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed timings for some events in demo files representing start of the round.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed ring artifacts that could appear on smoke particles.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed some lobby teammates standing offscreen when the main menu scenery was set to Warehouse map.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed storage units sometimes having a very small icon in inventory view.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a regression in items shuffling when matchmaking for Premier, Competitive, or Wingman.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed spectator kill streak effects playing when switching to a player with 5 kills.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a regression with Butterfly Knife inspect sounds.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Added a catch sound for Kukri knife draw animation.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed Zeus tracer appearing to pass through players.<br/></li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2796c6cf9167eef7acc8d966ec16209fd2f4ebe28cae0e5c756fe248165388c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/8/2024 Night</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where some inputs were acting as if they were released prematurely<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa1b1e4eeb58b8834d9b8ce8a4f085f05b1d2377bfc9ae272fcaf05de1b7b803</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/8/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ ARMS RACE ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where an extra kill with a shotgun before the knife level counted as the winning knife kill<br/></li></ul><br/>[ SMOKE ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Adjusted visibility of player silhouettes in smoke<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where enemies were visible on the radar when viewed through a combination of smoke and translucent surfaces such as glass<br/></li></ul><br/>[ ANIMATION ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Various bug fixes and tweaks to inspect animations<br/></li></ul><br/>[ MAPS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where doors spun the wrong way on several maps<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Nuke:<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed vis regressions<br/></li></ul><br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Ancient:<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed pixel gap looking into bombsite B from T Side<br/></li></ul><br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Anubis:<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed potential spot where bomb could be thrown into an unreachable area at T Spawn<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Enabled collision on ledge meshes at Sniper's Nest to prevent dropped weapons clipping through them<br/></li></ul><br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Mirage:<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed collision in Palace where bomb could be thrown into an unreachable area<br/></li></ul></li></ul><br/>[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where certain keys not found on US keyboards (such as the backslash key on UK keyboards) couldn't be bound<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed an issue preventing some older demos from playing back<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Various crash fixes<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">454bff22b6e9153fde9025b7c0ba3ead43f4976caaa79557d92e035dd9a5bfc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/7/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ STICKERS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where AMD graphics users couldn't move stickers<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Stickers with custom offsets will now render properly when inspecting other items in-game from Steam Community Market and Steam Inventory<br/></li></ul><br/>[ SMOKE ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Various bug fixes and tweaks<br/></li></ul><br/>[ SOUND ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a performance bug with certain microphone setups<br/></li></ul><br/>[ NETWORKING ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> cl_interp can no longer be changed directly. Some players had scripts that were setting this to a large value, leading to very bad rubber-banding. The interpolation amount can be adjusted through the "Buffering to smooth over packet loss" setting instead<br/></li></ul><br/>[ ANIMATION ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug with the Kukri knife inspect animation<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug where a player holding an incendiary grenade would sometimes show fire effects at their feet<br/></li></ul><br/>[ UI ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Removed XP Overload icon from the kill feed<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> The swap weapon prompt will now show the weapon/finish name rather than the custom name<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug with switching background maps while inspecting gloves<br/></li></ul><br/>[ MAPS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Vertigo:<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a gap in world geometry at Crane<br/></li></ul></li></ul><br/>[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Fixed a bug with keyboard input from non-English keyboard layouts<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> Various crash fixes<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">454bff22b6e9153fde9025b7c0ba3ead43f4976caaa79557d92e035dd9a5bfc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 2/6/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ ARMS RACE ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added Arms Race to available game modes<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added maps "Baggage" and "Shoots"<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ WEAPON FINISHES ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Introducing the Kilowatt Case, featuring 17 community-designed weapon finishes, and the Kukri Knife with original finishes as a rare special item<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Various bug fixes and tweaks<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ STICKERS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">The Ambush Sticker Capsule is now available for purchase<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added support for flexible sticker placement. Stickers can now be placed at user-specified positions and rotation when applied to weapons<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">All weapons now support up to five stickers<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added a zoom feature during sticker placement to allow for higher precision sticker application<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Various bug fixes and tweaks<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ MUSIC KITS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">The NIGHTMODE Music Kit Box is now available for purchase in standard and StatTrak versions<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ ZEUS ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Made Zeus reusable in all game modes, after a 30 second recharge delay<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added support for applying stickers and name tags to the Zeus<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted the Zeus first person model position<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added Zeus kill icon to kill cards and post round damage report<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ SMOKE ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Smokes now cast shadows<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Rendering and animation have been improved<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ GAMEPLAY ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added a "Refund All" button to the buy menu<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added a setting to disable first person bullet tracers<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Silencers can now always be reattached regardless of whether detaching them is enabled or not<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Player pings are no longer blocked by invisible geometry<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Various adjustments to sub-tick shooting<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed several cases where players could silently drop down vertical surfaces<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved smoothness of sliding along surfaces<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed an issue where collisions between players were jittery<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I"> To ensure loadouts are correct at the beginning of matches, loadout changes are no longer allowed while searching for Premier, Competitive, or Wingman<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ SOUND ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added the option to select an audio input device for VOIP from the audio settings menu<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added the option to change your microphone threshold (the minimum loudness before we start transmitting audio) from the audio options menu, as well as metering for your current mic loudness<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added the option to listen to your own microphone from the audio settings menu to hear how you sound<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Replaced the M249 fire sound effect<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Replaced the Zeus charging, charge not available and charge ready states sound effects<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Further reduced occlusion effects<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Minor mix adjustments<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed an issue where some player-centric sounds were being perceived as originating from slightly behind the player<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ NETWORKING ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Reduced peeker's advantage in many cases<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">The amount of peeker's advantage in the steady state is reduced by 16ms<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Also reduced the frequency of situations that lead to very large peeker's advantage due to excessive command queue depth<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added cl_ticktiming console command that prints a report breaking down the various sources of latency<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added an option to buffer server updates and user commands by one or more packets. This can be used to smooth over stuttering due to packet loss, at the expense of increased latency<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ UI ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added support for separate main menu and item inspect background map settings<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added "Baggage" and "Warehouse" as options for the main menu and item inspect background maps<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">In-game team-only chat will now be prefixed with the team (e.g., "[T]" or "[CT]")<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added 'XP Overload' status which is awarded to players who have earned all of their normal XP during the week (11,166 XP) and reached reduced XP gain. XP Overload status is attached to players' names in scoreboard, main menu, death notices, etc. XP Overload status is awarded for a minimum of one week. Additional tiers of XP Overload status can be unlocked by earning all of the normal XP over multiple consecutive weeks<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Agents with unique end-of-match cheer animations now have unique defeat animations as well. You can disable playing defeat animations for the local player in settings<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added more accolades to end-of-match<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted the range of CS Ratings allowed to party together in Premier matchmaking<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a case where high-DPI mice would result in jittery mouse movement<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Minor improvements to animations during demo playback<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Disabled rich presence update when running Steam Client in tournament mode<br/></li></ul><br/><br/>[ MAPS ]<br/><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Inferno:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed various gaps and adjusted grenade collision to make grenade bounces more predictable<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted texture blending to improve player visibility<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Ancient:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted grenade collision on bombsite B ground to make grenade bounces more predictable<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Anubis:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed holes in world at Lower Tunnel<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed collision on all pillars so players can no longer pixel boost<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed collision so utility does not fall out of world on top of structure at T Start<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed missing collision on steps at Street which would allow dropped weapons to fall out of world<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved vis at CT spawn<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed invisible boost ledge at Bombsite B<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed various gaps in the world<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed missing collision on stair geo at CT spawn that allowed weapons/bomb to fall out of world<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed missing collision at Fountain that allowed weapons/bomb to fall out of world<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some doors not generating bullet decals<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed vis issue at Street<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Overpass:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some collision that was causing unpredictable player movement<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Mirage:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added collision to prevent bomb becoming unreachable<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted some collision to prevent a ledge/pixel walk<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed player getting stuck when strafing on Middle Ramp by simplifying geo of floor and wall<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Removed a clip brush from Apartments to improve flash lineups<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Nuke:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Built some collision to prevent bomb from getting stuck behind barrels<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some disappearing mesh.<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed dynamic shadow clipping on characters at Vending<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Improved clipping in vents<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed bombsite water to have better reflections on low settings<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed vis issue at t-spawn<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed collision on ramp in Bombsite B<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed holes in world<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Vertigo:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed holes in world and other minor geometry bugs<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Italy:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted some collision to prevent players getting stuck in apartment<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Office:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a case where players could jump on a wall, fixed a case where players could get stuck if they crouched<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25506d0b36dab3b835888b5821d00f2849c380843fb6d6fb4dcb417d05f25f47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 1/18/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ MAPS ]<br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Vertigo:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a gap in geometry<br/></li></ul><br/>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cb566296faee99dc624720e6b648aa21090c6927726e8746701f02b5d88d4a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes for 1/4/2024</title>
      <link>https://www.counter-strike.net/news/updates?l=english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[[ UI ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed cases where there was a visible delay loading map images in the Play menu<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where items that can't be equipped were visible in the Loadout menu<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where loadout items couldn't be unequipped<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where loadout changes weren't saved if the game was quit shortly after making changes<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed a bug where loadout changes on the main menu character were delayed<br/></li></ul><br/>[ MISC ]<br/><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed some visual issues with demo playback<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Fixed an issue where animations would not play back correctly in a CSTV broadcast<br/></li><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted wear values of some community stickers to better match CS:GO<br/></li></ul><br/>[ MAPS ]<br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Ancient:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Added simplified grenade collisions to corner trims and central pillar on B site<br/></li></ul><br/><div class="bbcodes_Italic_zA7ad BB_Italic">Anubis:</div><ul class="bbcodes_List_20uQh"><li class="bbcodes_ListItem_1BF9I">Adjusted clipping at A site steps between Walkway and Heaven<br/></li></ul>]]></description>
      <author>support@steampowered.com (Valve Corporation)</author>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90e22735369f484702432e266ea62ede238b9c80c2c5ff18ba15314b74227070</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
